<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Guide</string>

    <string name="powered_by">Powered By Ankit Gupta</string>

    <string name="image_heading_1">Taj Hotel</string>
    <string name="image_heading_2">Taj Mahal</string>
    <string name="image_heading_3">Ganga</string>
    <string name="image_heading_4">Buddha BirthPlace</string>
    <string name="image_heading_5">Catholic Church</string>

    <string name="image_desc_1">The Taj Mahal Palace Hotel, is a heritage, five-star, luxury hotel built in the Saracenic Revival style in the
        Colaba region of Mumbai, Maharashtra, India, situated next to the Gateway of India. Historically it was known as
        the "Taj Mahal Hotel" or simply "the Taj".
        The hotel is considered one of the finest hotels in the East since the time of the British Raj.</string>

    <string name="image_desc_2">The Taj Mahal  lit.\'Crown of the Palace\', is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the southern bank of the river Yamuna in the Indian city of Agra.</string>

    <string name="image_desc_3">The Ganges is a lifeline to millions who live along its course.
        It is a sacred river and worshiped as the goddess Ganga in Hinduism.
        It has been important historically; many former provincial or imperial capitals
        (such as Patliputra, Kannauj, Kara, Kashi, Allahabad, Murshidabad, Munger, Baharampur, Kampilya and Kolkata)
        have been located on its banks.</string>

    <string name="image_desc_4">Lumbini, the Birthplace of the Lord Buddha. Siddhartha Gautama, the Lord Buddha, was born in 623 B.C. in the famous gardens of Lumbini, which soon became a place of pilgrimage. Among the pilgrims was the Indian emperor Ashoka.</string>

    <string name="image_desc_5">The Catholic Church, sometimes referred to as the Roman Catholic Church, is the largest Christian church, with approximately 1.3 billion baptised Catholics worldwide as of 2018. As the world\'s oldest and largest continuously functioning international institution.</string>

</resources>
